if you believe you can move the highest mountains cross the greatest oceans walk
across the water the water you feel defeated falling on your knees and
looking up for some hope tonight you try to stand up but you throw your hands
up like you no longer have the strength to fight because you've seen too many
sunsets too many days ending in the darkest night but on your own you never
know you'll never know if you believe you can move the highest mountains cross
the greatest oceans walk across the water the water believe you can move the
highest mountains cross the greatest oceans walk across the water if you
believe
they say that all you need is faith but it's almost like you lost your way took a
few wrong turns took a few breaks falling behind now looking for grace
cuz you need someone to lift you up yeah make right all the things you've done
cuz on your own you'll never know you'll never know if you believe you can move
the highest mountains cross the greatest oceans walk across the water
believe you can move the highest mountains cross the greatest oceans walk
across the water if you can do anything you can do anything you can do
anything you believe
If you believe you can move the highest mountains
cross the greatest oceans walk across the water
The water believe you can move the highest mountains cross the greatest oceans walk
across the water
if you believe