I've lived in many different countries, both in Western Europe, Middle East and now here
in Hong Kong, and during all of that time I've learned five or six different languages
to one degree or another.
I love learning languages, not only are they important when you move to a country, I just
find them fascinating.
Before I came to Hong Kong, I lived in Barcelona, Spain for ten years, and when I first arrived
the most important thing was being able to communicate with people locally.
I don't attend classes, I don't think I'm particularly good in classes.
I prefer to learn by just talking to people, finding out what I need to say by looking
at dictionaries and listening carefully.